{
    "subject": "Buddha_Loetla_Nabhalai",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Sri_Sulalai",
    "human_readable": "Buddha Loetla Nabhalai is married to Sri Sulalai.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9801498055458069,
            "question": "Are Buddha Loetla Nabhalai and Sri Sulalai a couple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9612181782722473,
            "question": "To whom is Buddha Loetla Nabhalai married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9241229891777039,
            "question": "Who is married to Sri Sulalai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9090485572814941,
            "question": "Is Sri Sulalai married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9065392017364502,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between Buddha Loetla Nabhalai and Sri Sulalai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8695139288902283,
            "question": "Does Sri Sulalai have a husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8648048639297485,
            "question": "What is the name of Buddha Loetla Nabhalai's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8600286245346069,
            "question": "What is the name of Buddha Loetla Nabhalai's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8287426829338074,
            "question": "Who is Buddha Loetla Nabhalai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.81819087266922,
            "question": "Is Buddha Loetla Nabhalai in a relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Buddha Loetla Nabhalai is married to Sri Sulalai.",
            "html": "yago_24701_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Buddha Loetla Nabhalai?",
            "html": "yago_24701_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Buddha Loetla Nabhalai's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_24701_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Buddha Loetla Nabhalai's wife?",
            "html": "yago_24701_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24701_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24701_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24701_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24701_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24701_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24701_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24701_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24701_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24701_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24701_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents state that Princess Sri Sulalai was a concubine of King Buddha Loetla Nabhalai and they had a child together,  it doesn't explicitly say they were married. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I can provide an answer in the form of a structured JSON format.\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Princess Sri Sulalai (also known as Chao Chom Manda Riam) was a royal concubine of King Buddha Loetla Nabhalai, and they also mention that she married Prince Isarasundhorn, who later became King Buddha Loetla Nabhalai in 1809. This information supports the triple that Buddha Loetla Nabhalai is married to Sri Sulalai."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Buddha Loetla Nabhalai is married to Sri Sulalai.\" For example, multiple documents state that Sri Sulalai was a royal concubine or consort of Buddha Loetla Nabhalai."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}